66.49.133.40 2007-12-25

# Ideal Exposure: Privacy Policy

Agency

Philosophy  
Strategy  
Service  
Clients  
Company  
People

Marketing

Media Buying  
Web Media  
Leads  
Search  
Behavioral  
Email

Creative

Branding  
Content  
Web Design  
Rich Media

Contact

General Inquiry  
Request Media Kit  
Employment

| 

**Privacy Policy**

Ideal Exposure, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy and has created this privacy policy to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices for the World Wide Web site located at www.idealexposure.com. We believe very strongly that private information should remain private. We would like to hear your feedback about this policy, if you have comments or questions, please contact us. 

**Quote / Information Registration**

In order to use certain areas of this Web site, a user may be required to complete a registration form. During registration a user gives contact information (such as name and email address, etc). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. 

**Information Use**

While Ideal Exposure, Inc. holds your personal information securely, we do provide third-party access to your personal information, we may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during customer visits to our Web site each month and may contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member, unless that member has not given us permission to share that information. 

**Profile**

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that detail their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user’s personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them, by Ideal Exposure, Inc. or our partners. Your profile is shared with third-parties in aggregate form only. Our partners may include advertisers, retailers, financial service companies, and other companies that have signed a valid marketing, non-disclosure and confidentiality agreements with Ideal Exposure, Inc. 

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking cookie that enables our log file analyzer to track user movement. 

**Special Offers and Updates**

For those areas of the site that require online registration, we send all new members a welcoming email to verify your request. Our sales team will promptly respond to your request and occasionally our prospects will receive information on products, services, special deals from Ideal Exposure, Inc. or our partners. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Opt-out section. 

**Newsletter**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Opt-out section. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy within our network, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law where we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Opt-out**

Our users are given the opportunity to `opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our site form has an `opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.   
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions given on each e-mail. If these mechanisms fail, the user may contact us at opt-out@idealexposure.com to opt-out. 

**Links**

This Web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Ideal Exposure, Inc., is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Security**

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.  
When our quote/information form asks users to enter sensitive information, that information is protected with to ensure your privacy. We use the highest level of security encryption, firewalls, and dependable servers. If you are on a secure page, such as an order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just `surfing'. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a locked facility. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
